# **GORAN RADMANOVIC**

1. Artiljerisjkog Puka 17, Gradiška 78400, BIH/RS • +387/065-899-867

goranradmanovic@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/goran-radmanovic-70814a9b/

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/

## Web Developer

5	ur	mr	ma	ary

I'm a back-end & front-end web developer, who likes new technologies, challenges and new experience. I'm a quick learner and I work as a freelancer. You can easily find me and contact me through social accounts or on email address. It would be a great honor to work with you. Hope to hear from you soon.

# Work experience -

04.2016 - 10.2018

Web Developer

Alea Control

I worked on the frontend part of the betting and gambling apps for casinos and bookmaker. Also I was in contact with programmers from partner's company and with our clients from casinos and betting house. And one of my responsibility was to develop and maintain company's website. Main technology which I used was JS and AngularJS, HTML & CSS, GIT.

Lecture at the Course Business Garden

09.2017 - 11.2017

07.2018 - 09.2018

I worked as a lecturer at the initial course of web development where I taught students to the basics of HTML and CSS technology.

10.2015 - 03.2016

PHP Web Developer

BitLab

I worked on the web pages and web apps for clients. I also maintained legacy code. In addition, I worked in a team of developers and the main technologies that I used were PHP & Laravel framework, HTML & CSS, and also JavaScript.

11.2014 - 12.2014

Intern

**OgoSense** 

I have successfully completed the program OGO Sense practices in the field of IT support and maintenance with focus on Client training and communication, Joomla CMS website managment and CentOS administration.

09.2014 - 11.2014 Intern *E-Info* 

In this practice, I worked with MSSQL databases, I was introduced to the basics of Delphi programming language and creating a form for entering and collecting data from the database via the Delphi. Also, I was introduced to the design of the database via MSSQL, installing Windows and Linux OS systems and MSSQL Server installation. I also worked in Embarcadero Framework.

10.2013 - 11.2013 Census Instructor

Census BIH/RS

Managing and leading census team; Educating census taker; Census field work.

Plastic d.o.o

Selling a variety of plastic goods and items; Conducted client assessments; Supply and delivery of plastic goods.

#### Education -

10.2016 – 12.2016 JavaScript Course

**ICBL** 

Basic of JavaScript programming language

12.2015 - 05.2015 PHP & MySQL Course

**ICBL** 

PHP and web development

07.2015 - 08.2015 WordPress Course

**ICBL** 

Installing WordPress and creating WP websites.

01.2015 - 05.2015 Beginner JAVA Course

**ICBL** 

Basic of JAVA programming language

**ICBL** 

Course about working in the teams and large groups.

05.2014 – 03.2015 Beginner, Advance and OOP PHP & MySQL Course

InfoARS Banja Luka

Learning about PHP and web development

10.2003 - 07.2008 Graduated demographer

#### Faculty of Science in Banja Luka

Demography and Population studies.

	Skills —
Languages	
	PHP, MySQL, Twig, Laravel, Slim
	HTML, CSS, Pug, SASS
	JavaScript, VueJS, Gulp
	Git, GitHub, JIRA, Trello
Databases	
	MySQL, Firebase
Hardware/Systems	
	PC/Server, Windows Server OS, Linux Server OS
	Portfolio

#### Projects:

http://www.goranradmanovic.byethost13.com/

http://www.bplace.byethost13.com/

http://slim-cms.byethost13.com/public/

https://www.aleacontrol.com

https://demo.aleacontrol.net/aleabetlist/#/

https://demo.aleacontrol.net/aleabet/#/

https://goranradmanovic.github.io

## Hobbies

Running, Basketball, Bicycling, Technology, Games, Blood donor